[
  {
    "type": "symbol_fill",
    "prompt": "F = m \u00d7 a",
    "options": [
      "F",
      "m",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "a",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.166,
      "I": 0.326,
      "SQI": 0.246
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4115195,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "topic": "physics"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "symbol_fill",
    "prompt": "F = m \u00d7 a",
    "options": [
      "F",
      "m",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "a",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.22,
      "I": 0.301,
      "SQI": 0.261
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4118884,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "topic": "physics"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "symbol_fill",
    "prompt": "F = m \u00d7 a",
    "options": [
      "F",
      "m",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "a",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.185,
      "I": 0.148,
      "SQI": 0.167
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4122071,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "topic": "physics"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "equation_match",
    "prompt": "Simplify or match: (a + b)**2",
    "options": [
      "x**2 + 4*x + 4",
      "a**2 + 2*a*b + b**2",
      "x**2 - 1",
      "p**3 + 3*p**2*q + 3*p*q**2 + q**3"
    ],
    "answer": "a**2 + 2*a*b + b**2",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.096,
      "I": 0.363,
      "SQI": 0.229
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4125576,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "topic": "algebra"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "symbol_fill",
    "prompt": "F = m \u00d7 a",
    "options": [
      "F",
      "m",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "a",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.247,
      "I": 0.43,
      "SQI": 0.338
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4128947,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "topic": "physics"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "symbol_fill",
    "prompt": "F = m \u00d7 a",
    "options": [
      "F",
      "m",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "a",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.13,
      "I": 0.423,
      "SQI": 0.276
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4131944,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "topic": "physics"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "equation_match",
    "prompt": "Simplify or match: (x + 1)*(x - 1)",
    "options": [
      "x**2 + 4*x + 4",
      "a**2 + 2*a*b + b**2",
      "x**2 - 1",
      "p**3 + 3*p**2*q + 3*p*q**2 + q**3"
    ],
    "answer": "x**2 - 1",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.146,
      "I": 0.367,
      "SQI": 0.256
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4134989,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "topic": "algebra"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "symbol_fill",
    "prompt": "F = m \u00d7 a",
    "options": [
      "F",
      "m",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "a",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.187,
      "I": 0.148,
      "SQI": 0.167
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4138129,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "topic": "physics"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "equation_match",
    "prompt": "Simplify or match: (x + 1)*(x - 1)",
    "options": [
      "x**2 + 4*x + 4",
      "a**2 + 2*a*b + b**2",
      "x**2 - 1",
      "p**3 + 3*p**2*q + 3*p*q**2 + q**3"
    ],
    "answer": "x**2 - 1",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.178,
      "I": 0.335,
      "SQI": 0.257
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.414118,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "topic": "algebra"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "equation_match",
    "prompt": "Simplify or match: (a + b)**2",
    "options": [
      "x**2 + 4*x + 4",
      "a**2 + 2*a*b + b**2",
      "x**2 - 1",
      "p**3 + 3*p**2*q + 3*p*q**2 + q**3"
    ],
    "answer": "a**2 + 2*a*b + b**2",
    "resonance": {
      "\u03c1": 0.153,
      "I": 0.379,
      "SQI": 0.266
    },
    "timestamp": 1761342902.4144187,
    "meta": {
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "topic": "algebra"
    }
  }
]